Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photos from old events, 1965-1992; RG0026 Series 10; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  - GW Alumni [15/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.5)
  - GW Alumni [16/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.6)
  - GW Alumni [17/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.7)
  - GW Alumni [18/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.8)
  - GW Alumni [19/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.9)
  - GW Alumni [20/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.1)
  - GW Alumni [21/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 70.1)
  - Girl on camel, undated (Box 3, Folder 70.2)
  - Fencer, undated (Box 3, Folder 70.3)
  - GW Alum [1/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 70.4)
  - GW Alum [2/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 70.5)
  - GW Alum [3/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 70.6)
  - GW Alum [4/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.1)
  - GW Alum [5/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.2)
  - GW Alum [6/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.3)
  - GW Alum [7/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.4)
  - Group shots of Alum [1/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.5)
  - Group shots of Alum [2/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.6)
  - Group shots of Alum [3/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.7)
  - Group shots of Alum [4/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.8)
  - Group shots of Alum [5/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.9)
  - Group shots of Alum [6/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.1)
  - Group shots of Alum [7/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.11)
  - Group shots of Alum [8/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.12)
  - Group shots of Alum [9/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.13)
  - Group shots of Alum [10/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.14)
  - Group shots of Alum [11/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.15)
  - Group shots of Alum [12/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.16)
  - Group shots of Alum [13/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.17)
  - Group shots of Alum [14/14], undated (Box 3, Folder 71.18)
  - Statue of George Washington, undated (Box 3, Folder 71.19)
  - Singers, undated (Box 3, Folder 72.1)
  - Chair, undated (Box 3, Folder 72.2)
  - Alum [1/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.3)
  - Alum [2/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.4)
  - Alum [3/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.5)
  - Alum [4/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.6)
  - Alum [5/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.7)
  - Alum [6/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.8)
  - Alum [7/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.9)
  - Alum [8/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.1)
  - Alum [9/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 72.11)
  - Alum [10/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.1)
  - Alum [11/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.2)
  - Alum [12/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.3)
  - Alum [13/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.4)
  - Alum Party [1/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.5)
  - Alum Party [2/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.6)
  - Alum Party [3/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.7)
  - Alum Party [4/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.8)
  - Alum Party [5/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.9)
  - Alum Party [6/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.1)
  - Alum Party [7/7], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.11)
  - Alum Meeting [1/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.12)
  - Alum Meeting [2/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.13)
  - Alum Meeting [3/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.14)
  - Alum Meeting [4/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.15)
  - Alum Meeting [5/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.16)
  - Alum Meeting [6/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.17)
  - Alum Meeting [7/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.18)
  - Alum Meeting [8/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.19)
  - Alum Meeting [9/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.2)
  - Alum Meeting [10/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.21)
  - Alum Meeting [11/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.22)
  - Alum Meeting [12/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.23)
  - Alum Meeting [13/13], undated (Box 3, Folder 73.24)
  - GW Reunion, Rose Mary, John & Annabel Schaupner, 04/04/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.1)
  - GW Reunion, Phil & Mary Howell Ingraham, Bea Pierre, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.2)
  - GW Reunion, John & Annabel, Schaupner, David Schott, '66, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.3)
  - GW Reunion, Margaret (Barbara) Kamalisn, Bonnie Selinsky, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.4)
  - GW Reunion, Bob Stanley, Annabel Schaupner, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.5)
  - GW Reunion, Mary (Howell) & Phil Ingraham, Gail Dennis '66, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.6)
  - GW Reunion, Merilyn, Fildman, Class of '66, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.7)
  - GW Reunion, Larry & Mary Ann Broadwell, Tom Steich '66, 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.8)
  - McClure, Georges Dedline (Class of 71), 04/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74.9)
  - Homecoming -Parade, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.1)
  - Homecoming, Archives Exhibit, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.2)
  - Homecoming, Joe Ayoub, Mary Jones, Tom Pagan, John Triber, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.3)
  - Homecoming, '92 -'82 Party, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.4)
  - Homecoming '92, Men's Game, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.5)
  - Homecoming '92, '82 Party, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75.6)
  - Group Photo [1/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.1)
  - Group Photo [2/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.2)
  - Group Photo [3/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.3)
  - Group Photo [4/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.4)
  - Group Photo [5/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.5)
  - Group Photo [6/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.6)
  - Group Photo [7/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.7)
  - Group Photo [9/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.8)
  - Group Photo [10/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.9)
  - Group Photo [11/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.1)
  - Group Photo [12/12], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.11)
  - An alumnus, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.12)
  - Two alumni, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.13)
  - Group photo, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76.14)
  - Aileen Gross, '85, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.1)
  - Gilbert Anderson, '40, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.2)
  - Phil Fairchild, '40, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.3)
  - Charles G. Kurz, '40, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.4)
  - Edith Ronne, '40, On Board View Amsterdam in Alaskan waters, 09/1989 (Box 3, Folder 77.5)
  - Marianne P. Broadwell '65 and husband Larry, 06/1989 (Box 3, Folder 77.6)
  - R. Elaine Hallmar, '65, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.7)
  - Frank Masa, '65, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.8)
  - Bennett Anderson Fore, '65, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.9)
  - Jeffrey A. Sacks '80, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.1)
  - Timothy O'Leary '80, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.11)
  - Kristina Jacobson '85, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.12)
  - Audrey (Goldstein) Pance '80, Nancy Jackson '79 at Taj Mahal, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.13)
  - Daniel Kraushaar, '85, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.14)
  - Robert Flisser '85, undated (Box 3, Folder 77.15)
  - Florida [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.1)
  - Florida [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.2)
  - A letter from GW Florida Alumni, undated (Box 3, Folder 78.3)
  - Flyer of this Don CeSAr Hotel [1/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.4)
  - Flyer of this Don CeSAr Hotel [2/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.5)
  - Flyer of this Don CeSAr Hotel [3/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.6)
  - GW Alumni Newsletter [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.7)
  - GW Alumni Newsletter [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 78.8)
  - GW Times, 01/1982 (Box 3, Folder 79.1)
  - Alumni Listing, 07/26/1974 (Box 3, Folder 79.2)
  - A group orientation, undated (Box 3, Folder 80.1)
  - Events [1/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.2)
  - Events [2/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.3)
  - Events [3/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.4)
  - Events [4/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.5)
  - Events [5/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.6)
  - Events [6/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.7)
  - Events [7/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.8)
  - Events [8/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.9)
  - Events [9/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 80.1)
  - Group of alumni [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.1)
  - Group of alumni [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.2)
  - Individual alumnus [1/4], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.3)
  - Individual alumnus [2/4], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.4)
  - Individual alumnus [3/4], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.5)
  - Individual alumnus [4/4], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.6)
  - Alumni [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.7)
  - Alumni [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.8)
  - Alumnus [1/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.9)
  - Alumnus [2/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.1)
  - Alumnus [3/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.11)
  - Alumnus [4/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.12)
  - Alumnus [5/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.13)
  - Alumnus [6/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.14)
  - Alumnus [7/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.15)
  - Alumnus [8/8], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.16)
  - Power Line, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.17)
  - Alumnus, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.18)
  - Reception Scene, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.19)
  - Alumnus, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.2)
  - Reception Scene [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.21)
  - Reception Scene [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.22)
  - Pres. Trachtenberg shaking hands with an alumnus, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.23)
  - Reception scene [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.24)
  - Reception scene [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.25)
  - Two alumni, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.26)
  - Two alumni chatting, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.27)
  - Two alumni, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.28)
  - A reception scene [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.29)
  - A reception scene [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.3)
  - Alumni chatting [1/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.31)
  - Alumni chatting [2/2], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.32)
  - Alumni in office, undated (Box 3, Folder 81.33)
  - Reception scene [1/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.34)
  - Reception scene [2/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.35)
  - Reception scene [3/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.36)
  - Alumni chatting [1/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.37)
  - Alumni chatting [2/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.38)
  - Alumni chatting [3/3], undated (Box 3, Folder 81.39)
  - Wilson, Ritter, golf, Cruekehanks in lab, 05/01/1939 (Box 3, Folder 82.1)
  - Power Plant Class, group photo, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 82.2)
  - Power Plants Class at Capitol Power Plant, 03/25/1939 (Box 3, Folder 82.3)
  - Letter from Ben Cruickshanks on ASME photos, 12/06/1987 (Box 3, Folder 82.4)
  - ASME Regional Conference participants, 05/24/1946 (Box 3, Folder 82.5)
  - A group of alumni, 10/1983 (Box 3, Folder 82.6)
  - Groups, undated (Box 3, Folder 82.7)
  - GW Times Vol, 19, No. 3 16 Pages, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 82.8)
  - A letter from Joanne to Wendy, 08/04/1989 (Box 3, Folder 82.9)
  - Letter from Judy Hunter to Wendy Luther, 08/04/1989 (Box 3, Folder 82.1)
  - Post Card and Biography of Bill Parker, 05/1991 (Box 3, Folder 82.11)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [1/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.1)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [2/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.2)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [3/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.3)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [4/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.4)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [5/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.5)
  - Reunion, Class of 1954 [6/9], undated (Box 3, Folder 83.6)
- Historic materials, 1848-1991; RG0026 Series 11; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  This series consists of alumni achievement awards, annual meetings, addresses, events calendars, publications, questionnaires, reunions, etc.. The materials range in date from 1848-1991, and were added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2000.
  - Achievement Awards, 1940 ca.-1989 ca. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Achievement Awards Nomination, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Events Calendars [1/2], 1974-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Events Calendars [2/2], 1974-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Events (Special), 1940 ca.-1989 ca. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Awards, 1947-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - First Wednesday Lecture Series, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - First Wednesday Lecture Series, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Addresses, dinner menus, annual meeting notes, 1848-1900 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Addresses, invitations, 1900-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General, 1939-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local Chapters, 1903-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Publications, questionnaires, 1922-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1979-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Service Awards, 1970-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Trips, 1963-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Trips, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Trustee, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University Book Fair Founders, undated; RG0026 Series 11 Box 4 (Box SERIES 11 BOX 4)
    Scope and Contents
    Framed, matted calligraphic list of George Washington University Book Fair Founders.
- Images of distinguished alumni, 1993-1994; RG0026 Series 12; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of slides and photos of distinguished alumni awards recipients,. They range in date from 1993-94, and were transferred to University Archives in 1995.
  - Distinguished Alumni Awards (DAA) recipients, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Awards (Chairman of Joint Chiefs of Staff Gen. John Shalikashvili), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Awards recipients, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Award - misc. photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Binder - slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acc 473 Slides, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photos of President Trachtenberg, 1992; RG0026 Series 13; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of photos and negatives of President Trachtenberg, 1992 homecoming and exhibit. The materials range in date from 1992, and were added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2000.
  Formerly ACC#831
- Alumni directories, 1865-2006; RG0026 Series 14; 4 Linear feet
  This series consists of alumni directories from the various schools, including: Columbian College of Arts and Sciences, Law School, Medical School, Elliott School of International Affairs, School Of Engineering And Applied Science, Graduate School Of Education And Human Development, School of Business and Public Management, Mount Vernon Seminary and College. They range in date from 1891-2003.
  - Alumni directory, 1824-1937; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Alumni directory, 1978; Series 14 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Alumni directory, 1984; Series 14 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Alumni directory, 2003; Series 14 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Alumni directory, 2008; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Alumni directory, 2013 (Box 3)
  - School of Business and Public Management Biographical record, 1994; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Columbian School of Arts and Sciences, 1991; Series 14 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Columbian School of Arts and Sciences, 1997; Series 14 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Elliott School, 1992; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Elliott School, 1898-1998; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - Engineering School, 1888-1955; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Engineering Alumni Association Directory, 1989; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Engineering School, 1997; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Graduate School of Education and Human Development, 1997; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Law School Alumni Directory, 1914; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Law School Alumni Directory, 1924; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 1973; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - Law School, 1866-1952; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - Law School, 1865-1925; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 18)
  - Law School centennial, 1865-1965; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - Law School, 1969; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - Law Alumni Directory, 1979; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 2006; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - National Law Center, 1924; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - National Law Center, 1987; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - National Law Center, 1987; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Medical Alumni Directory, 1826-1959; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Medical Alumni Directory, 1826-1965; Series 14 (Box 3)
  - Medical School, 1960; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - Medical School, 1965; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Medical School, 1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Medical School, 1986; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Medical School, 1993; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Medical School, 1999; Series 14 (Box 1, Item 7)
- General alumni association files, 1992-1996; RG0026 Series 15; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of general alumni association files, including executive committee meetings, by-laws committee, governing board, distinguished alumni achievement awards, etc.. The materials range in date from 1992-96, and were transferred to University Archives in 2000.
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/18/1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 04/05/1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 02/01/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/19/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 07/15/1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 04/13/1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/21/1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/29/1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 07/08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/10/1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 10/25/1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 06/15/1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Biannual Meeting
  - Governing Board Meeting, 04/13/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 02/16/1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 10/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 09/22/1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 01/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 10/08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 06/10/1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 05/20/1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 03/18/1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 01/15/1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - GAA Committees- General Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Awards Committee By-Laws Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Finance Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Recognition Awards Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Trustee Recommendation Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Governing Board Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    CONFIDENTIAL
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    General Correspondence
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Nominations
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations, 12/12/1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations, 03/08/1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations, 12/18/1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations, 12/12/1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations, 01/07/1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Committee for the 21st Century, 04/1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    File #1
  - Alumni Committee for the 21st Century, 04/1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    File #2
  - George Washington University Alumni Survey Results, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Binder - Alumni Committee for the 21st Century, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    General Information
- Yearbooks and memorabilia, 1898-1995; RG0026 Series 16; 15 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14)
  This series consists of Cherry Tree and National University Law School yearbooks framed photos (including commencement on Ellipse) and memorabilia. The materials range in date from 1898-1995, and were transferred to University Archives in 1999.
  Please note that within RG0123 the records of National University contains the Docket from 1922-1942.
  - The Cherry Tree, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Columbiad yearbook, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The C yearbook, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Mall yearbook, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Mall yearbook, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    3 copies
  - The Cherry Tree, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Docket, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Yearbook of National University Law School
  - The Docket, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Docket, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Docket, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Docket, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Docket, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Docket, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The Docket, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Docket, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Docket, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Docket, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Docket, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - The Docket, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Docket, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The Docket, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The Docket, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Docket, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Columbian College Alumni Association Medal with reproductions of Columbian College Seal, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    6 items
  - US Flag, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tassels, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Video--GWU "Connections", Office of Admissions, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Book--Suddenly Alone: A Woman's Guide to Widowhood by Philomene Gates, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - GWU Newsletter, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin no.1-50--"Confidential from Washington", 1942-1949 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Mounted photographs: Poster--Joe Cocker concert at Lisner Auditorium, 04/30/1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mounted photographs: B.B. King in concert, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Mounted photographs: "Lynda Bird Johnson attending classes", undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mounted photographs: Peace demonstration on the Mall, 1960 ca. (Box 9, Folder 4)